In the window of the sketch, double-click to open the PRACTICE FILE folder and find the d.corrected in PowerButtonSimulation file in EFIXES.
Double-click to open the PRACTICE FILE folder and find the d.corrected in PowerButtonSimulation file in EFIXES.
The PRACTICE FILE is distorted due to incorrect arrangement before simulation.
Select the PRACTICE FILE in the 2D window.
Right-click on the PRACTICE FILE.
Select the 2D arrangement position in the menu.
Select the PRACTICE FILE.
Use the positioning tool in the 3D window to rearrange the layer relationship of the PRACTICE FILE.
Open the PRACTICE FILE arrangement point.
Select the left and right door panels in the 2D window at the same time.
Click on the PRACTICE FILE in the pre-arrangement point.
Put the panels down.
Activate simulation.
Check the shape after adjustment.